whenever you're ready.
>> Okay. All right. Here we go. All right.
Michael, welcome to Washington.
Congrats. I'm just curious like for you
as a pass rusher, where have you taken
that step the last season and a half or
so?
>> Oh, man. Uh first of all, how you doing
John? How you doing everybody? Before I
get started, uh
>> uh as a step as a passion man, just
continue to believe um in myself and my
skill set. Um obviously man um letting
it snowball and taking advantage of all
opportunities that come my way.
>> So you had to do that one year prove it
last year with New England. What do you
feel is there something you still you
have to prove and how can that help you
this year knowing that?
>> Hey John, can you repeat the question
you kind of chopped up a little bit?
>> Okay, sure. Sure. No problem. So you had
to sign that one year prove it deal last
year with New England. You went out and
had a really good year. What do you feel
you still have to prove and how can that
help Washington?
>> Uh man, I think it's more so everything
just proved to myself. Um thanks for
watching to believing in me. Um and and
and bringing that that that faith and
that confidence uh within the
organization to bring me along and to
help this organization to reach the the
ultimate goal and that's to bring a
championship in. So, um, man, I think
everything is more so just proven to
myself, proving to this organization
that we made the right decision, um, and
bringing me along and helping us reach
the ultimate goal, and that's to bring
Lombardi back.
>> Thank you.
>> David Aldridge.
>> Hey, welcome to Washington, man. How are
you,
>> David? Why you look familiar, brother?
>> Ah, it's a long story. You'll I'll tell
you later.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I got you.
>> Um, first of all, just because I always
do this guys coming in, please tell us
how to pronounce your first and last
name so we don't mess it up going
forward.
>> Yeah, most definitely. Um, Kale Leavon
Chason.
>> Gotcha. Gotcha. All right. So, uh, asked
a couple of other guys that have signed
up here in the last day or two the same
thing. I want to ask you, you were
literally in the Super Bowl a month ago,
you know, um on a very good team with a
very young quarterback with a great
coach and you opted to come to
Washington, which also has a very good
young quarterback, but is in a in a
building stage rather than where where
you were. So, I just wonder like I know
it's free agency, but just like what
what led you to say, "All right, I'm g
I'm gonna leave the safe thing to go to
this thing that is that's still on the
rise."
>> Um, I think I think this whole thing uh
between the transaction between me and
the Patriots and also between me and the
commanders is also just believing in
each other. Um, belie in an opportunity
and a plan that we're we're trying to
put in place um and move forward with
it. Um, obviously I think I got a chance
to talk with with Dan and and DJ um and
Pags um just about the trajectory that
the the organization would like to take.
Um and you can tell me that uh you would
have thought the same thing would happen
to us last year um with the Patriots. So
um excited for the opportunity, excited
for the building pieces that we have
within the building, man. Um the staff
um I believe in them all the way. um
everything that they're trying to
instill is culture-wise um as in the
defensive system wise and the players
that we bringing in um it's all about
the belief and I think that they brought
the right guy in to hurry up um
obviously to kind of progress that and
and enforce those those those traits and
I just think it all it all depends on us
the players um and I take pride in that
and I think that's the direction we will
go for sure. What did what did Dan and
Dante say about like specifically how
they think you grew fit in?
>> Oh man, just just just really excel in
my skill set. Um don't need me to do
anything different. Um they like the way
I play. Um they like everything that
I've shown on tape. Um they feel like
it's it's what best fit this system and
this team, this organization, the
culture in the locker room that we're
trying to build. Um and I appreciate
that. I appreciate everything and more
that we're trying to build. um that that
they believe in who I am and and the
trajectory of as a player, as an
individual, um that I'm headed and um I
just I'm thankful, super grateful for
the opportunity that both Donte and DQ
um got a chance uh to take on me and um
it's it's it's so much that we have in
store for sure this year and I'm excited
for sure.
>> Thank you,
>> Donna.
Hey, Kon. Um welcome to Washington. Uh
you said that they got the right guy and
you said that it's more so about proving
to yourself. What do you feel that you
need to prove to yourself even more so
as you uh entered this uh relationship
with the commanders?
>> Yeah. Uh I think everything about um who
I who I am and who I believe I am um is
everything that I'm trying to prove. Um
a hard-nosed athlete um is with great
determination. um willing to fight
through any and every adversity that
comes his way. Um this is just outside
of football aspects, man. But this is
just a character. Um um I think shout
out to my parents. Um shout out to my
grandparents for everything that we've
been through um to get to this
situation. So I think everything that's
going forward, man, just continuously
prove myself right through every
adversity um and every obstacle that
comes our way. um appreciate all all
achievements and accomplishments that
came um and appreciate every adversity
once again and um and and discouraging
things that happened throughout the way.
So the journey is is everything and more
and um continuously like I said want to
prove myself right, want to prove um
prove myself to God um first and
foremost that um I'm his son and um I'm
no better um no better and all I want to
do is praise and glorify him in each and
every way for sure.
And um you know this Washington team
because you all are play have played
them. Um what excites you most about
coming to Washington?
>> Man, I think I think the talent that
that that's here um is it's second to
none for sure. Um I think we we have we
have the pieces and everything we need
to to go in the right way. Um I think
it's a phenomenal division to want to
play in. Um you're going against the top
guys in NFC. Um Jaden Daniels, man,
obviously LSU product, Heisman winner,
man, you you can't knock it. Uh the the
weapons that we have on offense and
Terry, u we just we just got Rashad, of
course. Um it's everything and more for
sure. So, um I just see I see I see the
light I see the light through the tunnel
and I'm looking forward to it, man. I'm
looking forward to being that spark and
that key missing piece um to taking us
in the right direction. Congratulations
again and welcome to Washington.
>> Thank you, Don.
>> Ben,
>> hey Caleb, welcome uh to town. Um,
what did you know this is a new
defensive coordinator, so we haven't
seen what exactly it's going to look
like. What did they kind of sell you on
in terms of how you fit into what they
do knowing that sometimes a little 43,
three, four, kind of all over the place?
>> H man, I just think the most thing is
just getting to the quarterback, right?
Um, I think that's the biggest thing in
today's game where we play these guys a
lot of money, we pay the the pass
protectors a lot of money, we pay the
edge rushers a lot of money. Um, I think
that's what affects the game the most.
And um, I think that opportunity is what
um, what excited me. Um, obviously man,
we have some key pieces. We just made
some phenomenal additions um, to the
line. Obviously OAU
um, myself man, we already had some
existing pieces in Armstrong and Payne
and Kinlaw. So, um, the the the the moon
and and the galaxy is far from the
ceiling anymore. So, uh, man, I'm
excited for this opportunity, man. And
that's all I that's all I can be
thinking about throughout this whole
time is is the potential and opportunity
that we have as a defense um to take
over games. Um, obviously Donte coming
over from Minnesota. Um, I was literally
telling, man, I got a chance to watch uh
the the game that we they played against
Detroit and it was just so it was just
so dominating. um in the way of defense,
man, how they took over and and dictated
in every way they wanted to early downs
and on pass downs. So, um that's
exciting to be a part of, especially as
a pass rusher, man. You get to the
quarterback and seeing how many guys um
within their system um had double digit
sacks um throughout their years there.
So, I'm looking forward to it once again
and um I think it's it's everything and
more to come for sure.
And you've obviously as players do make
made a lot of strides over the course of
the your career. What do you think
looking back on it was maybe the biggest
adjustment for you to go from, you know,
coming out of the gates a little bit
slow to really having picked it up the
last couple years?
>> Man, just continue to believe. That's
it. Um continue to believe everybody's
story is not the same. Everybody
everybody's journey um is not the same.
Um comparison is the biggest thief of
joy. So uh the best thing I loved about
all this, man, is the journey.
everything that I learned, the
relationships that I gained, um the
adversity that I've been through, um
everything that has taught me um is
everything and more and I wouldn't be
here today u without it. So, um once
again, man, just excited for everything
that's to come um individually and as a
team and man, I just think that to keep
building on the opportunity and let the
confidence roll and I think DQ and Dante
is going to do a great job with that for
sure.
Andy.
>> Hey there, Kay Leavon. Um, welcome to
Washington. And did I say your name
correctly?
>> No, you said it right. Thank you, Ken.
>> Perfect. Perfect. Um, so how would you
describe your game? What can you tell us
about how you approach the game on game
day?
>> Man, I just I think the main thing I
always want to just be known for is man,
just playing hard. Um, playing all the
way fourth quarters non-stop. Um, I
mean, I think the talent is there. Um,
obviously But this the NFL, I think
we're all talented for sure. Um we're
the 1% of the 1%. So, um I take pride in
that. Um I don't take I don't take that
for granted. But man, being able to play
hard um and being consistent all four
quarters and being dominating in the
fashion um imposing my will against
opponents. Um I think that's everything
and more you can ask for for sure.
and having just come out of a Super Bowl
appearance but not being, you know,
being on the team that did not win. What
did you learn from that overall
experience in general? Because of course
it's an honor to go to the Super Bowl,
but just that adversity of not being
able to come away with it.
>> Yeah. Um it's still fresh, so I'm still
I'm still trying to soak it in and and
figure it out, man. Uh that was
heartbreaking for sure. Um it's one
that's still going to sting. Um I don't
know when and what time of my career I
get over that moment for sure. But it's
definitely building a fire built the
fire in and in a burning hole in me that
that makes sure I want to fulfill that
fulfill that need um and that journey
for sure. So um man uh if anything and
more uh I just want to continue to build
in that right direction um and continue
to pour in that pour in that area and um
obviously I want to get back in and
bring home to Lombardi for sure.
>> Thank you and welcome to Washington
again. Thank you all so much.
>> Thanks, Caleb. Appreciate it.
>> Appreciate you, boss.